人人影視
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯： 暴龍蛋      圈圈      蘇小黛
翻譯： Kiko      DustD      胖兔純
時間軸： 濃子   萌    校對： 蘇小黛   胖兔純
后期： 孤帆    總監： 米小勒   胖兔純
塞勒姆
第一季  第九集
《塞勒姆》前情提要
Previously on Salem.
巫師
Witch！
塞勒姆沒有哪個女人能有那種權力
No woman in Salem has ever had that kind of power.
連瑪麗·西布里都沒有
Not even Mary Sibley.
屋子的女主人是我的
The lady of the house is mine.
我們發現了一個巫師
We've uncovered a witch.
不知此次您會在鎮上停留多久呢
How long may we enjoy your curative presence in town?
直到我見證塞勒姆最后一個巫師死去
Until every last devil's whore of a witch in Salem is dead.
彼得魯斯的藥效只能持續一天
Petrus' physic will last but a day,
然后西布里先生即將恢復神智  迫不及待地
And then Mr. Sibley will awake, lucid and eager.
將一切向英克里斯全盤托出
To tell Increase everything.
選一個
Choose one.
喝吧
Drink.
好好享受吧
Drink and...enjoy.
只有凡人才會受不了這種酒的誘惑
Only mere mortals are vulnerable to manmade spirits.
作為人類  你讓人嫌惡
As a man, you are an abomination,
但你不是巫師
but you are no witch.
現在收起你可悲的軟弱滾蛋吧
Now begone with you and your...pitiful weakness.
醒醒  我的好女士
Time to wake, my good madam.
讓他們不再說"上帝安排一切"
Let them no more say, "God must do all,"
以此教唆他們
and so encourage themselves
從此遠離上帝
to live in a careless neglect of god
遠離自己內心的
and of their own souls
救贖
and salvation!
惡魔已經把
The devil has made
這個村莊搞得烏煙瘴氣
a dreadful knot of witches in the country,
并在巫師的幫助下
and, by the help of witches,
繼續變本加厲地進行破壞
has dreadfully increased that knot.
孩子們  孩子們  提高警惕
Oh, children, children, be afraid
睡覺以前一定要祈禱
and go not prayerless to your bed
以免惡魔趁虛而入
lest the devil be your bedfellow.
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*Witch drums*
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*The witch drums*
*寧入地獄*
*Better pray for hell*
*不留人間*
*Not hallelujah*
早上好  牧師
Good morning, reverend.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
一起吃嗎
Join me?
您對我丈夫的
There are no words
再造之恩
to encompass my overwhelming gratitude
我的感激無以言表
at your reclamation of my husband.
如果不是您去到了那兒
When I think what might have transpired
-后果真不堪想象  -是嗎
- had you not been there... - Indeed?
會有什么后果你說說看
Exactly what might have transpired?
-什么  -我是說...
- Excuse me? - well...
你家女仆難道不會直接送他去醫院嗎
Would not your slave girl simply have taken him on to hospital?
當然
Yes.
正是  是你派了她去救他
Yes, it was you who sent her to his rescue,
不是嗎
was it not?
我一收到消息就立馬派她去了
Once I'd heard of the accident.
不過  我很困惑
I am perplexed, though.
為什么這么著急秘密地把喬治送出去
Tell me, why was George scurried off with such haste and secrecy?
他經常去波士頓
He goes often to Boston.
-去看病  -他沒病
- His illness. - He's not ill.
-他是被下咒了  -不
- He's spelled. - No.
怎么可能
That's impossible.
你想想...
Consider...
喬治是不是無緣無故
has not George suffered this mysterious malady
就被這怪病纏了好幾年
without explication for several years now,
而且  是不是沒有醫生能說出
and have not the doctors expressed utter befuddlement
這到底是何原因
as to its cause?
-是的  但...  -那么在那種情況下
- Yes, but... - Yes. In such cases,
答案就再簡單不過了
The answer is oft the simplest one.
他根本沒病
George is not ill.
而是受制于惡魔的邪惡爪牙
He is under the influence of the devil's darkest tool --
也就是巫師的咒語
a witch's spell.
而且似乎這個施咒者與之非常親近
And it is quite likely that this speller resides close at hearth.
不
No.
也許就住在你家
Perhaps even in the hallowed halls of your own home.
有話就說吧
Say it.
說什么
Say what?
你不是想控告我嗎
The accusation.
你憋了很久了吧
It dances on your tongue.
你誤會我的意思了
Well, I assure you, you are mistaken.
我想即刻把我丈夫接回去
Then I wish to bring my husband home immediately.
恕難從命  西布里夫人
I think not, Mrs. Sibley.
你憑什么拒絕我
You would deny me that right?
我必須拒絕你
I must deny you that right
直到我們發現咒語的根源
until we can discover the origin of the spell.
那我請求...  不  我要求
Then I would ask, or, rather, insist,
找個人照顧西布里先生
that someone attend to Mr. Sibley.
最好是有照顧他經驗的人
Someone who has experience with his travails.
那個年輕人怎么樣
What about that young man...
就是那個載他去波士頓的
the one who was to take him to Boston, huh?
-艾薩克  -恩
- Isaac? - Ah.
就他吧
Isaac will do.
他還在昏睡中嗎
He sleeps still?
有侍衛看守著呢
Under the care of sentries.
對了  瑪麗
Oh, and, Mary.
放心吧
Be of good heart.
酒吧老板蘭布先生說他可能隨時醒來
Mr. Lamb, the barkeep, tells me that he may wake at any moment.
柯頓
Cotton.
我跟那些死人沒什么分別
No difference between me and those that already rest.
只是我的心還跳動在
Besides a still-beating heart
一具靈魂空洞的軀殼里
in a shell where my soul no longer resides.
天啊
Oh, boy.
早啊  牧師
Good morning, reverend.
我在想...
I wonder --
怎樣才能讓你起身
what would it take to get you to your feet?
你為什么想這么做
Why would you wish to?
我擔心自己可能...
I fear I may have...
對你太刻薄了  麥哲牧師
judged you too harshly, Reverend Mather.
只是現在  當童年遠去
It is only now, when leaving my childhood behind,
我才意識到  無論過去還是以后
that I realize we are, past and forever,
我們都是為人子女
our fathers' children.
我們不能選擇他們是誰
And we can no more control who they be
他們怎樣塑造我們
and how they came to form us
但是我們能做回自己
then we can the rise and setting of the sun.
你愛的那個姑娘  我很遺憾
I am sorry about your girl.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我們送你回家好嗎
May we see you home?
起來
Come on.
把他送回家安置好后  上尉
Once he's settled, Captain,
你能幫我個忙嗎
may I ask a favor of you?
當然
Surely.
"恕難從命  西布里夫人"
"I think not, Mrs. Sibley."
就好像他是蘇格拉底  我是跪在他跟前的學生
As if he were Socrates and I, a student at his knee.
讓我去殺了他吧
Let me kill him, please.
不行
No.
讓我幫你減輕這個負擔  就跟處理其他人一樣
Let me ease this burden for you, as I've done the others.
不論在新世界還是舊世界
Increase Mather is known throughout the world,
英克里斯·麥哲都聲名遠揚
new and old.
他消失或者死亡肯定會引起不小的轟動
His disappearance or death will not be taken lightly.
不能平白無故就讓他死去
His head will sit on no man's platter.
他自然無法與你相提并論
He's no match for you, certainly.
這樣想你就錯了  孩子
That is where you are wrong, child.
這是對我們的真實考驗
This is our truest test
去與勢均力敵之人戰斗
to battle equals.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
牧師
Reverend.
梅西
Mercy.
您好
Hello.
我能否跟我女兒
I wonder if I might have a private word
單獨說幾句話
with my daughter.
恕難從命  牧師
I think not, Reverend.
-我...  -去幫我把艾薩克找來
- I - Fetch me Isaac.
馬上
Now.
我...
I am, um...
沒想到您對我的孩子如此仁慈寬厚
astounded at the charity you've shown my child,
但如果我想見她
but if I wish to see her,
這不是一個父親應有的權利嗎
is that not a father's right?
你為什么想見她呢  牧師
Why, in particular, do you wish to see her, Reverend?
你是想對她用其他驅邪方法嗎
Were you perhaps considering another exorcism?
身邊沒有孩子
Do your days grow dull,
讓你打罵折磨是不是很無聊
lacking a child to beat and torture
漫漫長夜沒有女兒陪伴是不是很孤單
and the nights far too lonely with no daughter to visit?
-我絕不會...  -梅西是我的人
- I would never - Mercy is mine.
你再來的話我就公開指責你了
Return here again and these accusations will be made public.
西布里先生怎么樣了  醒了嗎
What of master Sibley? Has he woken?
長老們不想再等了
The elders will wait no longer.
他們要求今天與你見面
They require an audience with you today.
他醒了嗎
Has he woken?
隨時都可能醒
Any moment now.
那是意外  夫人
It were an accident, ma'am.
一根黑松木擋在路中間
A wayward timber in the path,
然后我們就都跌下馬車不省人事了
and we found ourselves at sixes and sevens.
沒事  艾薩克
It's okay, Isaac.
我知道你已經盡力了
I know you've done your best.
牧師現在找我
The reverend summons me now,
不知道為什么  但我擔心他是想等...
heaven knows why, but I fear each second he's made to wait --
他會讓你照顧西布里先生
He will ask you to watch over Mr. Sibley.
-是嗎  -在我的強烈堅持下
- He will? - At my grave insistence,
因為他拒絕讓我
since he refuses my desire
把我丈夫帶回家照料
to bring my husband home to proper care.
他拒絕你
He refuses you?
塞勒姆就像一個笨重的陀螺一樣轉失控了
Salem reels out of control like an unwieldy spin top
都是因為英克里斯·麥哲的隨心所欲
at the whim of Increase Mather.
這是減輕痛苦有助于睡眠的藥劑
A tonic... the pain and ease of sleep.
艾薩克  我請求你
Isaac, I beseech you,
這是一件極其重要而又私人的事
in this most private and important matter,
幫我一下吧
do my bidding where I cannot.
這個...
Oh, uh...
馬上讓他服下  并且藥不能停
Dose him immediately and keep him so.
不該讓喬治遭受
George should not be made to suffer
老麥哲毫無根據的懷疑
for Mather senior's unfounded suspicions.
不會的
H-he shall not.
艾薩克...
And Isaac...
此事你知我知
Between us.
就像塞勒姆的很多其他秘密一樣
Like so many of Salem's secrets.
你知我知
Between us.
你知道嗎  孩子
Are you aware, son?
你的故事真是無人不知無人不曉
Your story is known far and wide throughout the land.
私通者艾薩克
Isaac the fornicator.
不不不  不要因羞愧而低下頭
No, no, no. Do not bow your head in shame.
抬起頭來  抬起來
Head up. Get your head up.
抬頭  抬頭
Head up. Head up.
私通者艾薩克的故事
The story of Isaac the fornicator
是神圣的
is a holy one.
它被我們清教徒當做一個活生生的例子
It is used as a living precedent by we puritans
用來向孩子們說明欲望的罪惡
to illustrate to the children the evils of lust.
不不  你的罪惡和痛苦...
No, no. Your sin and your suffering...
已經被轉化為神圣而偉大的祝福了
It has been transformed into a great and a holy blessing.
因為  孩子...
For, my son...
你感受到了上帝之手
You felt the hand of God.
他碰觸了你
He's touched you.
他是在考驗你
He's working through you.
他選擇了你
He's chosen you.
不
No.
有幾個人能說自己是被上帝選中的啊
How many can say that they have been chosen by God?
選我干什么
Chosen for what?
孩子  你想過塞勒姆以外的生活嗎
Son, have you ever imagined a world beyond Salem?
-我  -頭抬起來  抬起來
- I... - Get your head up, your head up,
抬頭  抬頭
Your head up, your head up.
我在這里生活得很好  先生
I have a good life here, sir.
是啊  你在這里給西布里夫人跑腿
Yes, performing meager errands for Mrs. Sibley.
她待我很好  一直很好
She's been good to me. Always.
她對你的施舍讓你對她言聽計從
Her charity binds you to her bidding.
不  不不不   艾薩克
No. No, no, no, Isaac.
外面
Out there.
外面  孩子
Out there, boy!
外面是大千世界
There's a vast world out there,
機會  機會遍地都是
full of... full of opportunities,
如果你  如果你想在陽光下抬頭挺胸
and if you... if you would walk the straight road
走上康莊大道
in the sunlight with your head up,
我會帶你出去親眼看看
I would take you with me to see it.
我會的
I would.
你覺得怎么樣
Would you like that?
那我需要怎么做
What would I have to do?
這個...
Well...
你得...
You will have to --
你得來照顧西布里先生
Have to tend to Mr. Sibley there.
你得...
You'll have to...
保證他每天整潔如新
...make certain that he is fresh and tidy,
這可不是件容易的事
and that is no easy task, hmm?
最重要的是  他醒時你必須通知我
Most importantly, you must alert me the moment that he wakes.
沒錯
Yes.
你能做到嗎
Can you do that, hmm?
恕我冒昧問一句  先生
Do you mind me asking, sir,
這些是用來做什么的
What these are for?
用來保護西布里先生免受
Protection for Mr. Sibley against...
外界勢力危害
outer forces.
這是骨灰
It's cremated ash...
一名兩百歲女巫的骨灰
...of a 200-year-old witch.
對了  艾薩克
And, Isaac...
她是我親手燒死的
I burned her myself.
屋頂有兩處需要修補
So, the roof needs patching there and there,
墻面也最好能重新油漆一下
A fresh coat of paint wouldn't hurt,
另外我們還需要四五張床來安置小一點的孩子
nor would four or five more beds for the smaller children,
還有  我是不是嚇到你了
And... I'm overwhelming you.
不  不
No, no.
我很樂意能將精力花在做善事上
I'm eager to put my energies to good.
我也正是這么想的
Exactly.
孩子們都被嚇壞了  上尉
The children are frightened, captain.
今天又有一個人被絞死  也不知道誰會是下一個
Another hung today and not an inkling who's to be next.
如今他們也不知道誰更可怕
They're unsure who to fear more...
巫師  還是追捕他們的那些人
Witches or those who pursue them.
誰能怪他們呢
Well, who can blame them?
他不怎么合群
He doesn't play with the others.
那個深色頭發的男孩
The dark-haired boy.
他來這兩年了
He's been here two years.
父母都被印第安人殺害
His parents were murdered by Indians.
有人說他目睹了一切
They say he saw.
沒人知道他是怎么活下來的
No one knows how he survived.
有人問過他嗎
Has anyone asked?
他從不說話
He doesn't talk.
至少  從那以后
At least, not anymore.
就再也不說了
Not since...then.
打擾一下
Excuse me.
你會修屋頂嗎
Do you know anything about patching a roof?
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley?
女主人出去了
The mistress is out.
有什么要告訴她的  都可以對我說
Anything needed to be said to her can be said to me.
它真漂亮
Oh, that's beautiful!
我的親信
My familiar.
親信
Familiar?
這是惡魔的饋贈  它為我賣命
A gift from the devil to do my bidding,
我的靈魂伴侶
My spiritual companion.
我是這樣喂食它的
This is how she feeds.
我也能得到親信嗎
Will I get a familiar?
會有的
In time.
我要如何選擇它呢
How do I choose?
由不得你
You don't.
它會選擇你
It chooses you.
日安  西布里夫人
Good day, Mrs. Sibley.
姑娘們
Girls.
我們正準備去墓地與梅西見面
We're off to meet mercy in the graveyard.
這樣嗎
Well.
那就快去吧
On your way, then.
姐妹的死我與你們一樣深感悲痛
We all grieve the loss of our sister.
愿她能在地獄之門與魔鬼共舞
-另一位姐妹又怎么說  -蘿絲
不是死于敵人之手  卻是拜她深愛及保護之人所賜
你才是該死的那個人
我不會為自己辯白
I do not argue this.
但我想讓你們知道  我別無選擇
But beg remembrance that I was given little choice.
惡靈
The malum...
我們大祭典的必須之物
...without which our grand rite would not be possible.
蘿絲未經我同意  便將這件死亡之器
Rose brought it here, this instrument of death,
帶來了這里  想以此挑戰并擊敗我
without my knowledge, to challenge and defeat me.
為了你們  也為了我們崇高的大業
It is for you, retrieved at great cost,
我不惜一切代價將其奪回
relinquished with love and ardor for our cause.
如今  我將它交予你們
I leave you now with the only tool
這個世界上唯一能控制我的物品
that exists on earth to control me.
拿回去
我們不稀罕你這些小玩意
我們早有了控制你的籌碼
劈柴的訣竅在于讓它們自然裂開
The trick to making shakes is to split them...
不靠砍也不靠鋸  而是裂開
Not chopped or sawed, but to split.
謝謝
Thank you.
到你了
Your turn.
就是這樣  干得漂亮
Right! Well done.
上尉
Captain.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
年輕人
Young man.
你能去給我找些水來喝嗎
Why don't you go see if there's any fresh water.
今早的事真是轟動
Big doings this morning.
如今每天似乎都有意想不到的事情發生
Seems every day brings its fair share of surprises.
我聽說你丈夫在英克里斯那里
I heard old Increase took possession of your husband.
是的
Yes, he did.
我想把他帶回來
And I'm eager to get him back.
是嗎
You are?
為什么
Why?
一個妻子想讓丈夫回家
Is it so unusual, captain,
就這么讓人驚訝嗎  上尉
for a wife to want her husband at home?
對大部分人來說不是
In most cases, it's not unusual at all.
聽說我的幫手口渴了
I heard my hard worker was thirsty.
您也在啊  西布里夫人
Oh, Mrs. Sibley.
要來點新鮮的蘋果汁嗎
Uh, fresh apple water on offer.
不了  謝謝你  安
No, thank you, Anne.
再見  上尉
Good day, captain.
年輕人
Young man.
上尉
Captain.
尋寶杖
本日停業
這個能給我嗎
May I?
就算你已經決定了徹底放縱自我
If you're going to capitulate to your weakness,
你一定要弄得這么眾人皆知嗎
must it be on constant public display?
或許我該將舞臺留給您  父親
Shall I leave public display to you, father?
不如把絞刑架拆了
Shall we abolish the noose
這樣您就能親手折斷他們的脖子
so that you may break necks with your own two hands?
她之前就死了
She was dead.
那個鴇母是自殺的
The whore runner killed herself.
她都已經死了
She was already dead,
而你還要絞死她
and yet you hung her.
我說過她會被絞死
I said she would hang.
我說到做到
and hang she did.
如果言而無信  那我們就什么都不是
We are nothing if we do not keep our word,
可惜你卻似乎并不懂得這條原則
A principle which seems to mean very little to you, I fear.
您就這么憎恨我嗎
Must you hate me so?
我的柯頓
Oh, Cotton.
你母親是柯頓家族一員
Your mother was a Cotton, as you know.
也是我同母異父的妹妹
And my stepsister.
我們的婚姻是歷史的必然
Our marriage was a historical inevitability.
柯頓家和麥哲家
The Cottons and the Mathers...
誰能拒絕兩家
Who could resist such a..
如此的強強聯合呢
Such a joining of...of power and prestige?
你當然不會拒絕
Certainly not you.
她是個好女人
She was a good woman,
也是個稱職的母親
and she was a fit enough mother,
但是
But...
我并不愛她
I didn't love her.
我不懂愛
I didn't love.
后來  便有了你
And then you were born.
然后你出生了
And there you were, a...
這么小的一個小人兒  只會哭
Squalling mess of limbs and of hair, and...
這么微不足道
You weren't much.
但你卻足以讓我明白了愛
But you were enough to show me love.
真是諷刺
What utter irony
如今你卻執意要奪走我身邊的愛
That you would then take the self-same thing from me.
你不能再喝了  先生
You are cut off, sir!
不  我有錢
No. I have money!
我要喝個痛快
I will drink muchly and often!
不行  趕緊離開
You will not. Now be on your way.
我不干
I think not.
不行  走開
Oh, no, no. Whoa. Go!
美酒是上帝的賞賜
The wine is from god.
醉漢則是魔鬼的懲罰
The drunkard is from the devil.
趕緊振作起來
Pull yourself together.
還有很多事要做
There's much work to be done.
讓我殺了他
Let me kill him.
我告訴過你了
I have told you.
不能殺了英克里斯
We cannot kill Increase.
不是又老又蠢的英克里斯
Not silly old Increase.
我是說西布里先生
Mr. Sibley.
你就是這么教她的嗎
This is what you teach her?
遇到問題  首先就想到殺人
For any problem, murder is the first course of action?
我們不能殺了喬治
We cannot kill George.
為什么
Why not?
你如此有權勢  你大權在握
You are so powerful... you alone.
你不需要他
You do not need him.
這你就錯了  親愛的
That is where you are wrong, my dear.
我們非常需要他
We need him desperately.
沒有喬治  一切就都沒了
Without george, it all goes away.
我就只是個一無所有的寡婦
I am a widow with nothing...
無權掌控生意  無權在委員會中發聲
No business to run, no voice with the selectmen.
只要他活著  我就能通過他來發話
With him alive, I can speak through him...
做一個模仿他意愿的玩偶
A puppet to parrot his wishes and thoughts.
但他死了就沒用了  我也就沒有權勢了
But dead, he is useless and I am without power.
可你要如何阻止他說出實情
But how will you stop him from speaking?
我要進入他的大腦  從內部毀了他
I will enter his mind and destroy it from within.
他的肉身還活著  但不會再有意識了
His body will live on, but his mind will be gone.
這要怎么做
How will you do that?
閉嘴  問題夠多了
Quiet girl! That is enough questions.
你無權讓我閉嘴
Don't you tell me to be quiet.
-閉嘴  -夠了
- Quiet.  - Enough!
你們倆都出去
Both of you, leave me now.
-可我能幫你  -出去
- But I can help you.  - Get out!
放開我
Let go of me!
放開
Let go!
知道我們能殺了誰嗎
You know who we could kill?
你
You.
不行  她不會讓你這么做的
You can't. She would never let you.
也許不會  也許會
Maybe, maybe not.
你不會想知道的
You don't want to find out.
你這個嫉妒刻薄的壞女人
You're jealous and spiteful and awful.
我已經等很多很多年了
Years... I have waited many, many years.
別礙我的事  賤人
Stay out of my way, you little bitch.
西布里夫人一心只為你好
Mrs. Sibley's only ever had your best interest at heart.
可盡管如此
Yet still...
在你最為絕望的時刻
Your moment's worst desperation,
開口求救卻并未說出她的名字
It was not her name you uttered for rescue
你居然叫了老麥哲牧師
But that of the reverend Mather senior.
我這個
What do I,
在你那里只得到過暴力
Who have known only violence
和惡意的人
and malice from your eager hands,
又怎么會在乎你的死活呢
care a whit about your rosy outlook?
瑪麗
Mary.
如今擺脫了你的親信
Free of your precious familiar,
我終于又贏回了夢想
I finally got hold of my dreams back.
在你這黑暗扭曲的意識里
Hmm. A beatific choice
這還真是個美好的選擇
For such a dark and twisted mind.
你還記得來過這兒嗎
You remember coming here?
記得  那次野餐
Yes. A picnic.
你唯一沒讓我心懷鄙視的一天
The one and only day I almost didn't despise you.
你從沒給過我機會
You never gave me a chance.
你早就對我下了定論
Your mind was long made up.
能怪我嗎
Can you blame me?
你偷走了我的人生
You stole my life.
現在你則偷走了我的
And now you've stolen mine.
我們就快成功了
We are close.
非常接近了
So very close.
大祭典就快完成了
The grand rite is almost complete.
然后呢
And then what?
又一個王國供你主宰嗎
Another kingdom for you to rule?
沒錯
Yes.
一個我不再需要你的世界
A world in which I no longer need you.
在那個美好的世界里  你終于可以徹底死去
A blessed world in which you can finally die.
你就這么迫害威脅自己的丈夫嗎
Peril and threats.
比我們更不堪的夫婦數不勝數
Many a union has relied on less.
別這么擔心  喬治
Don't look so worried, George.
我們還沒有完全成功
We're a little ways off yet.
如今  我只需要你閉嘴
For now, I just need you quiet,
在你骯臟的圍兜里像個天使般沉睡吧
Sleeping like an angel in your dirty bibs and nappies.
永別了  喬治
Farewell, George.
賤人
You bitch!
混蛋
Oh, that bastard.
西布里嗎
Sibley?
英克里斯·麥哲
Increase Mather.
他在那里
He was there.
保護著喬治
Protecting george.
即便是他睡夢中的意識
Guarding his mind even in sleep.
我們還有個麻煩
We have another problem.
我們必須對那女孩采取點措施
We must do something about the girl.
梅西
Mercy.
她很不可靠
She is...unreliable.
終有一天我們將無法再控制他
It is only a matter of time before
這只是個時間問題
we can no longer control her.
此時此刻
At a time such as this
我比任何時候都有可能被發現
when I am nearer to discovery and annihilation
命運懸于一線
than ever before,
你卻讓自己
you would distract yourself
為那些不值一提的嫉妒和惡意中傷分心
with petty jealousy and spiteful accusations.
我試著要
I am trying to make --
我比任何時候都需要你
Never have I needed you more.
你卻從沒像如今這樣讓我失望
And never have you disappointed me so gravely.
我愿意為你做任何事
I would do anything for you.
-我愛你  -我倒希望你別愛我
- I love you. - Oh, and I wish to god you didn't.
別那么愛我  或許這樣會更好
Love me less and you will love me better.
想辦法接近喬治
Find a way to get to George.
明天我們涂漆
Tomorrow, we'll work on the paint.
當然了  如果你還有空的話
That is, if you're still available, of course.
干得好
Excellent.
干得好  孩子
Excellent, son.
史蒂芬
Stephen.
你見過我女兒
You've seen my daughter.
你可以走了  這里只有孩子
You can move along. There's kids here.
我就是在找孩子  我的孩子
I'm looking for a kid -- my kid.
我說了  快滾
And I said, "Move along."
霍普金斯先生
Mr. Hopkins.
有什么能幫你的嗎
How can we help you?
我入獄之后  我女兒是不是住在這里
My daughter came to stay here after when I was in jail?
艾米莉
Emily?
不  霍普金斯先生  她沒有
No, Mr. Hopkins. She did not.
你在附近見過她嗎
Have you seen her around?
不  先生  我沒有
No, sir. I haven't.
告訴她我在找她
You tell her I'm looking for her.
告訴她  讓她趕緊回家
You tell her she needs to come home.
是  霍普金斯先生  我會的
Yes, Mr. Hopkins. I'll do that.
利茲
Lizzy...
你把雞毛
Did you bring the chicken feathers
和干馬糞帶來了嗎
and the dried horse dung?
雞毛我帶來了  但是馬糞不太干
I brung the feathers, but the dung weren't dry.
老鼠呢
And what about the mice?
貓把陷阱里的老鼠都嚇跑了
They scattered when the cat come to the trap.
梅西馬上就要到了
Mercy is to be here any minute.
難道什么事都要我親自做嗎
Must I do everything myself?
霍普金斯小姐  能借一步說話嗎
Miss Hopkins, may I have a word?
你父親被釋放了
Your father has been freed.
知道了
I see.
他正在找你
And he's been looking for you,
說讓你馬上回家
asks that you come home immediately.
霍爾小姐
Miss Hale.
有什么可以幫忙的嗎
Can we help you?
我只是來告訴霍普金斯小姐
I've only come to tell Miss Hopkins
她父親被釋放了
that her father has been freed.
你人真好
How kind.
他似乎
And that he seemed...
酩酊大醉失去理智了
quite inebriated and not himself,
也許她今晚最好先別回家
and that perhaps she oughtn't to go home tonight.
或許可以在孤兒院待一晚
Perhaps she ought to stay in the orphanage
在那里她會很安全
where she'd be safe.
她很安全
She is safe.
和我們在一起
With us.
是嗎
Is she?
或許你可以留下
Would you care to stay and...
親眼見證
see for yourself...
安
Anne?
今晚不了
Not tonight.
住手
Stop.
那是什么
What is that?
這是止痛藥劑
A tonic. For pain.
你從哪里拿到的
Where did you get it?
蘭姆先生給我的
Mr. Lamb gave it to me
-你出去的時候  -不是
- while you were out. - No.
不是嗎
No?
年輕人
Young man...
年輕人  我給過你機會不是嗎
Young man, I offered you an opportunity, did I not?
你還記得
Do you remember?
世界  廣袤的世界  陽光
The world -- the vast world, the sunlight.
我曾經懷疑過你
I somehow suspected you would find a way
還是會忍不住自輕自賤
to undermine yourself.
雖然我希望你不會這么做
But I did -- I hoped against hope that you wouldn't,
你卻仍被我不幸言中
but you did.
因為你不僅是個白癡還是個廢物
Because not only are you a cretin, you're a failure.
你是個無可救藥的廢物  和所有廢物一樣
You're a cretinous failure, and like all failures,
你對自己說  "我從未有過機會
You say to yourself, "But I never get the chance!
從未得到機遇"
I never get the opportunity,"
但其實并不是這樣  不是嗎
But it just ain't so, is it?
不
No.
和所有廢物一樣  你做了什么
And like every failure, what do you do?
你在機會面前退卻了
You just piss in the well of possibility.
現在你告訴我是誰給你這藥劑的
And now you are going to tell me who gave you the potion.
硬如干柴  冷如巖石
Stiff as a stick, cold as a marble.
輕如精靈  輕徙鳥舉
Light as a spirit, lift yourself.
輕如羽毛  硬如石板
Light as a feather, stiff as a board.
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
編汝之網  回吾之召
Spin us a web and heed our call.
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Master spider, stilted or stifled,
編汝之網  回吾之召
Spin us a web and heed our call.
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
誰給你的
Who gave it you?
Hmm? Who gave it you?
抬頭  抬頭
Head up. Head up.
-它不是藥劑  -不是藥劑嗎
- It's not a potion. - It's not a potion?
它不是
It's not a po--
看我  孩子
Look at me, boy.
這是  補藥
It's -- it's medicine.
再說一次
One more time.
我問你  誰給你的
I'm going to ask you, who gave it to you?
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Master spider, stilted or stifled,
編汝之網  回吾之召
Spin us a web and heed our call.
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
我們會這么做
What we'll do is this --
這是補藥
It's medicine.
我會把你的肚子剖開
I'm going to slit your belly open.
那是藥
It's medicine.
我會伸手進去猛的一拉
I'm going to reach in, pull out,
然后用你的腸子勒住你的脖子
and I'm going to throttle you with your own intestines.
回吾之召
...heed our call.
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Master spider, stilted or stifled,
編汝之網  回吾之召
Spin us a web and heed our call.
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
不  不  不
No. No. No.
現在  你趕緊告訴我
Now, you tell me right now,
誰給你的
who gave it to you?!
告訴我  艾薩克
Tell me, Isaac!
告訴我
Tell me!
西布里夫人絕不會傷害生靈
Mrs. Sibley could bring no harm to a living thing.
只要是她給的藥水
If -- if she provided me the medicine,
我絕對相信她
that's good enough for me.
西布里夫人  是嗎
Mrs. Sibley, eh?
干得好
Well done.
你現在可以走了
Off with you now.
走
Go.
快走  從我眼前消失
Go on! Out of my sight!
私通者艾薩克
Isaac the fornicator!
喬治
George.
George!
喬治
你好  父親
Hello, father.
跟你說了他們會放了我的
Told you I'd get out.
是的  你說了
Yes, you did.
我說過這事沒完
I told you this weren't over.
你依然會被賣掉  如果妓女還要你
You'll be sold still, if the whores will have you.
我哪都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你會的
You will.
你會去我要你去的地方
You will go where I tell you!
我不會
I won't.
我不會  我
I won't. I --
求你
Please!
亨利·霍普金斯
Henry Hopkins.
這是干什么
What is this?
史蒂芬
Stephen.
他叫這名字  那孩子
That's his name, the boy.
他告訴你的嗎
He told you?
是的
Yep.
兩年了  他一言不發
Two years without speaking,
而你只用一天就知道了他的名字
and in one day, he tells you his name.
他一定很喜歡你  上尉
He must have really taken to you, captain.
不  我不這么覺得
No, I wouldn't say that.
誰又能怪他
And who could blame him?
男孩子總需要特別關注
Boys need attention
還有辛勤勞動來消耗他們多余的精力
and hard work to burn off their energy.
我很感激
And I'm grateful...
您的辛勤努力
for your hard work.
這是我回來以后第一次
It's the first hours passed since I've come back
不再滿腦子都想著巫師的事
where I haven't thought about witches.
我想人們都會愿意選擇這種生活
I supposed one could choose that life --
本分工作  團結互助  溫馨的家庭
Honest work, community, a loving family,
不會再有巫師
and not a witch in sight.
也許我們還有希望
Maybe there's hope for us yet.
你
You!
去通知行政委員
Alert the selectmen.
又一個女巫已經出現  跟我來
Another witch has been revealed. Follow me.
也許不是
Or maybe not.
瑪麗·西布里
Mary Sibley!
你丈夫醒了
Your husband is awake.
喬治醒了
George is awake?
他說話了嗎
Has he spoken?
他已被奪取言語能力
He is rendered incapable of speech.
然而  讓他飽受折磨之人的姓名已出現
Nevertheless, the name of his tormentor has been divulged.
那是什么意思
What does that mean --
被奪取言語能力
"Rendered unable to speak"?
你認得這瓶藥劑嗎
Do you recognize this potion?
是的
Yes.
那是止痛藥劑
It's a physic for pain.
我讓艾薩克拿去給西布里先生的
I gave it to Isaac to give to Mr. Sibley.
止痛藥劑
A physic for pain?
告訴我  止痛藥劑會不會
Tell me, would a physic for pain
讓西布里先生的嘴被
seal Mr. Sibley's mouth shut...
黃金蛛網封住呢
with a golden web?
止痛藥劑
A tonic for pain.
別無其他
Nothing more.
我能說一句嗎  父親
Might I suggest, father,
西布里夫人的藥水可能如其所述
That Mrs. Sibley's tonic is just that,
而造成蛛網出現的
and the work of the web is due,
很可能是真正巫師的蜘蛛親信
more likely, to the real witch's spider familiar.
是的
Yes.
是一種可能  搜查房屋
It's a possibility. Search the house.
等下
Wait!
我很抱歉  先生
I'm sorry, sir.
你是說蜘蛛嗎
Did you say a spider?
路易絲家的孩子  曾經被巫師附身折磨
The Lewis child, once tortured and possessed by witches.
可如今她看起來十分健康
Yet now she looks remarkably well.
多虧了西布里夫人的悉心照料
All due to Mrs. Sibley's kindness.
她拯救了我的生命
She saved my life.
我曾被飽經折磨
I was tortured and tormented,
在死亡邊緣尋求解脫
at the verge of begging for death,
而瑪麗·西布里將我帶離邪惡
and Mary sibley delivered me from evil.
所以我有些猶豫要不要說
Which is why I hesitate to say --
你想要說什么  姑娘
What is it you have to say, girl?
那天早晨
The other morning,
當西布里夫人外出處理船運業務的時候
when Mrs. Sibley was out on shipping business...
-然后  -我經過了緹圖芭的房間
- Yes? - ...I did pass Tituba's room,
當時她正在做一件極其詭異的事
and she was doing the strangest thing.
告訴我們  梅西  告訴我們你看到了什么
Tell us, Mercy. Tell us what you saw.
她將一個蜘蛛捧在肩頭
She held a spider to her neck.
然后呢
Yes?
她好像在喂它
She seemed to feed it.
你
You.
過來
Come here.
我在此以
I hereby arrest you...
涉嫌巫術的罪名逮捕你
on the charge of witchcraft.
守衛
Guards.
是的  長官
Yes, sir.
好的  長官
Aye, sir.